<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Calls on ICAPS 2023</title>
    <link>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/calls/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Calls on ICAPS 2023</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 10:27:57 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/calls/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Doctoral consortium</title>
      <link>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/calls/dc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 10:27:57 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/calls/dc/</guid>
      <description>ICAPS 2023 Doctoral Consortium The Doctoral Consortium (DC) is intended to give Ph.D. students the opportunity to closely interact with established researchers and get feedback on their research, provide advice on career possibilities and build a professional network, improving the cohesion of new researchers with the ICAPS community.
The DC is open to all doctoral student attendees of the conference and will take place on July 8th (the day before ICAPS workshops and tutorials).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>System Demonstrations</title>
      <link>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/calls/demo_track/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/calls/demo_track/</guid>
      <description>ICAPS 2023 Call for Demonstrations The 33rd International Conference on Automated Planning and Scheduling July 8-13, 2023, Prague, Czech Republic. The System Demonstrations and Exhibits program at ICAPS 2023 provides an opportunity for planning and scheduling researchers and practitioners to demonstrate their state-of-the-art implementations in action. This event allows the community to experience some of the latest contributions to the field while broadening the reach of novel methods. Researchers from all sub-areas of AI planning and scheduling are encouraged to submit proposals to demonstrate their systems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journal Track</title>
      <link>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/calls/journal_track/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/calls/journal_track/</guid>
      <description>ICAPS 2023 Journal Presentation Track he program committee of the 33rd International Conference on Automated Planning and Scheduling (ICAPS) invites submissions of published journal papers for the Journal Presentations Track, initiated in 2014.
The track is designed to provide a forum to discuss important results related to automated planning and scheduling that appeared recently (from January 2022 onwards) in selective journals, but have not been previously presented either at ICAPS or at any other major AI conference (such as IJCAI, AAAI, ECAI).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorials</title>
      <link>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/calls/tutorial_call/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 14:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/calls/tutorial_call/</guid>
      <description>ICAPS 2023 Call for Tutorial Proposals: The Organizing Committee for the 33rd International Conference on Automated Planning and Scheduling (ICAPS 2023) invites proposals for its Tutorial Program. Tutorials offer the attendees a review of a specific subfield by a leading expert. Participation in the tutorials is free for all ICAPS participants.
The tutorial (and workshop) programs will comprise several concurrent events held in the two-day period before the plenary sessions of the conference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Partnerships</title>
      <link>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/calls/partnership_call/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 10:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/calls/partnership_call/</guid>
      <description>ICAPS 2023 Partnership Program If you are interested in supporting financially ICAPS 2023, please contact Sponsorship Chairs:
 America : Robert Goldman, SIFT (rpgoldman@sift.net) Asia : Hankz Hankui Zhuo, Sun Yat-Sen University of China (zhuohank@mail.sysu.edu.cn) Europe : Neil Yorke-Smith, TU Delft (n.yorke-smith@tudelft.nl)  Offer for Partnership Benefits * All prices include 21% VAT.
Platinum Partner: min. 220000 CZK (10000 USD and more)  Company name and logo with link to company website displayed on website and conference materials (category Platinum) Access to opt-in database of attendee contact information who are interested in being recruited Exhibition Space (4 x 3 m) 6 Complimentary registrations allowing access to all conference events Choose three of the named events/awards  Gold Partner: 150000 - 219000 CZK (7000 - 9999 USD)  Company name and logo with link to company website displayed on website and conference materials (category Gold) Access to opt-in database of attendee contact information who are interested in being recruited Exhibition Space (2 x 3 m) 4 Complimentary registrations allowing access to all conference events Choose two of the named events/awards  Silver Partner: 75000 - 149999 CZK (3400 - 6999 USD)  Company name and logo with link to company website displayed on website and conference materials (category Silver) Access to opt-in database of attendee contact information who are interested in being recruited Exhibition Space (2 x 3 m) 2 Complimentary registrations allowing access to all conference events Choose one of the named events/awards  Bronze Partner: 25000 - 74999 CZK (1100 - 3399 USD)  Company name and logo with link to company website displayed on website (category Bronze) 1 Complimentary registration allowing access to all conference events  Sponsorship Opportunities for Named Events and Awards  Invited Speaker Best Paper Award Best Student Paper Award Best Demo Award Best Dissertation Award  Approximate exchange rates (1 EUR - 24.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshops</title>
      <link>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/calls/workshop_call/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 16:19:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/calls/workshop_call/</guid>
      <description>ICAPS 2023 Call for Workshop Proposals: The organizing committee of the 33rd International Conference on Automated Planning and Scheduling (ICAPS 2023), scheduled to be held July 8-13, 2023, in Prague, invites proposals for its workshop program. The workshops provide a forum to discuss research advances on a selected topic in an informal setting and promote dissemination and collaboration on new planning and scheduling challenges.
We welcome proposals from all areas of planning and scheduling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Robotics Track</title>
      <link>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/calls/robotics_track/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 18:32:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/calls/robotics_track/</guid>
      <description>ICAPS 2023 Call for Papers: Robotics Track The Robotics track welcomes research contributions in the general areas of planning and scheduling (P&amp;amp;S), which relate to the advancement of intelligent robots. P&amp;amp;S models and techniques are important for enabling autonomous, flexible, and interactive behaviors in robotic systems. A deep integration of these methods into robotic architectures can assist their effective deployment. In this direction, the ICAPS-2023 Robotics track provides an opportunity for the planning and robotics communities to share research progress in the area of robot planning and showcase the use of planning and scheduling technology in robotics applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Application Track</title>
      <link>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/calls/application_track/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Sep 2022 18:17:23 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/calls/application_track/</guid>
      <description>ICAPS 2023 Call for Papers: Industry and Applications Track ICAPS is the premier forum for exchanging news and research results on theory and applications of intelligent planning and scheduling technology. ICAPS 2023, the 33rd International Conference on Automated Planning and Scheduling, will host an Industry and Applications Track (formerly known as Novel Applications Track).
The goal of this track is to bring together planning and scheduling practitioners, industry stakeholders and academic communities for exchanging all aspects of the development, deployment, and evaluation of planning and scheduling systems for societal or industrial problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning Track</title>
      <link>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/calls/learning_track/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 17:47:17 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/calls/learning_track/</guid>
      <description>ICAPS 2023 Call for Papers: Planning and Learning Track The Planning and Learning track aims to present research at the intersection of the fields of machine and reinforcement learning with planning and scheduling. In particular, we are interested in work that draws substantially from the objectives, techniques, or methodologies of both fields.
Topics include, but are not limited to the following:
 Reinforcement learning using planning (model-based, Bayesian, deep, etc.) Learning domain and action models for planning Representations for learned models in planning Learning effective heuristics and other forms of planning control knowledge Theoretical aspects of planning and learning Multi-agent planning and learning Planning applied to automating machine learning systems Learning to improve the effectiveness of planning &amp;amp; scheduling systems Applications that involve a combination of learning with planning or scheduling  Please note: papers that do not clearly make a case for their relevance to model-based planning techniques or that do not compare to model-based planning techniques may be rejected without review.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Main Track</title>
      <link>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/calls/main_track/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Aug 2022 08:26:07 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/calls/main_track/</guid>
      <description>Call for Papers: ICAPS 2023 ICAPS 2023, the 33rd International Conference on Automated Planning and Scheduling, will take place in Prague, July 8-13, 2023. ICAPS 2023 will be part of the ICAPS conference series, the premier forum for exchanging news and research results on the theory and applications of intelligent planning and scheduling technology.
ICAPS 2023 will feature 4 different tracks:
 Main Track (see below) Industry and Applications Track Planning and Learning Track Robotics Track  Additionally, the ICAPS program will include a journal track, demonstrations, workshops, and tutorials, each having separate submission and notification dates, to be announced separately.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
