<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Attendings on ICAPS 2023</title>
    <link>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/attending/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Attendings on ICAPS 2023</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 17:53:41 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/attending/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Accommodation</title>
      <link>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/attending/accommodation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 17:53:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/attending/accommodation/</guid>
      <description>Accommodation MAMA Shelter Prague
Conference Hotel
Mama Shelter Prague offers a unique experience of a ten floors hotel situated close to the main attractions, to a large park and to the Prague Holešovice exhibition grounds. The hotel offers 238 rooms designed by Jalil Amor; rooms are as comfortable as they are smart, featuring Mama Skin organic solid amenities, free movies, and smart screens. There are also two large restaurants, two lively bars, and a lot of space for informal meetings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Registration</title>
      <link>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/attending/registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 17:53:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/attending/registration/</guid>
      <description>Registration The registration for the 33rd International Conference on Automated Planning and Scheduling (ICAPS) 2023 will be handled by Ms. Milena Zeithamlová, a conference local arrangements chair.
To register, you are kindly asked to complete
REGISTRATION FORM
 and pay the registration fee. Registering early will save you money, and also it will help us to organize things better!
The deadline for early registration is May 5, 2023 and the late registration deadline is July 5, 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Student Support</title>
      <link>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/attending/students/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 17:53:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/attending/students/</guid>
      <description>Student Support ICAPS secured funding from NSF and AI Journal to support students’ participation at the conference. The NSF funding is targeted to students from US-based institutes only; the AIJ funding is for students from other institutes. The funding will be distributed to selected students as (partial) reimbursement of travel and registration expenses after the conference or as discounted registration fee. The exact amount depends on the amount collected from sponsors, your home location, and the number of other applicants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel Information</title>
      <link>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/attending/travel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 17:53:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/attending/travel/</guid>
      <description>Travel Information The Czech Republic is a member of the European Union and the Schengen area. It has a typically European continental climate (summer temperatures average between 20°C / 68°F and 25°C / 77°F but often reach as high as 30°C / 86°F). The time zone is Central European Time (CET, CEST in summer). The local currency is Czech Crown (Koruna, Kč/CZK, exchange rates to USD/EUR/GBP). Many shops and restaurants accept Euro; card payments (including Apple Pay/Google Pay) are also widely accepted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Venue</title>
      <link>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/attending/venue/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 17:53:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/attending/venue/</guid>
      <description>Venue ICAPS 2023 will take place at the Charles University in Prague, Czech Republic. Prague is a political, cultural, and economic hub of central Europe, with a rich history and Romanesque, Gothic, Renaissance and Baroque architectures. It was the capital of the Kingdom of Bohemia and residence of several Holy Roman Emperors, most notably Charles IV (r. 1346–1378). Wikipedia
   Doctoral Consortium Venue
Doctoral Consortium, ICAPS Council Meeting, and IWPSS will be held at Malá Strana Campus of Faculty of Mathematics and Physis (building &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Venue</title>
      <link>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/attending/venue.old/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2023 17:53:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://icaps23.icaps-conference.org/attending/venue.old/</guid>
      <description>Venue ICAPS 2023 will take place at the Charles University in Prague, Czech Republic.
Prague is a political, cultural, and economic hub of central Europe, with a rich history and Romanesque, Gothic, Renaissance and Baroque architectures. It was the capital of the Kingdom of Bohemia and residence of several Holy Roman Emperors, most notably Charles IV (r. 1346–1378). [Wikipedia]
The main conference venue is hosted by Faculty of Mathematics and Physics and will be held at the IMPAKT building of Troja Campus, V Holešovičkách 747/2, 180 00 Praha 8   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
